Guide to Records of the Office of the President (John Brademas) RG.3.0.10
New York University Archives
- Series XIII. Speeches and Writings, 1981-1991; 54394; 22.50 Linear Feet in 54 manuscript boxes.; 1 audiocassette; 3 videocassettes (vhs)
  - "Education and The Nation's Agenda: Perspectives in an Election Year," Beta Gamma Sigma Alumni Dinner (NYU), 1988-10-03; 54866 (Box 289, Folder 23)
  - Charles Waldo Haskins Dinner (New York, NY), 1988-10-04; 54865 (Box 289, Folder 24)
  - Leonard N. Stern School of Business Press Conference (NYU), 1988-10-06; 54864 (Box 289, Folder 25)
  - American Council for the Arts Conference (New Brunswick, NJ), 1988-10-07; 54863 (Box 289, Folder 26)
  - Medical Center Board Meeting RESTRICTED, 1988-10-07 (Box 102, Folder 22)
  - Celebration and Dinner Honoring Ioannis Georgakis and Speros Vryonis, Jr. (NYU), 1988-10-10; 54861 (Box 289, Folder 27)
  - Stern School of Business Board of Overseers Dinner (NYU), 1988-10-18; 54860 (Box 289, Folder 28)
  - Reception for Martin Luther King Scholars (NYU), 1988-10-20; 54858 (Box 289, Folder 29)
  - Art and Business Council Luncheon (New York, NY), 1988-10-20; 54859 (Box 289, Folder 30)
  - All-University Convocation (NYU), 1988-10-20; 54857 (Box 289, Folder 31)
  - Annual Archbishop Iakovos Feast Day Dinner (Washington, D.C.), 1988-10-22; 54856 (Box 289, Folder 32)
  - Dinner Honoring Graduate School of Public Administration Dean Howard Newman (NYU), 1988-10-24; 54855 (Box 289, Folder 33)
  - Campaign for Oxford Convocation (Oxford, England), 1988-10-26; 54854 (Box 289, Folder 34)
  - Allan Bloom Rebuttal Editorial, 1988-10-28; 54852 (Box 289, Folder 35)
  - "Education for a Strong and Secure America: An Election-Eve Perspective," the Woman's National Democratic Club (Washington, D.C.), 1988-10-31; 54851 (Box 289, Folder 36)
  - Memo Re: Post-Election Thoughts on the New President and Education, 1988-11-08; 54850 (Box 289, Folder 37)
  - Interview with The Chronicle of Higher Education, 1988-11-08 (Box 289, Folder 38)
  - University Senate Meeting (NYU), 1988-11-10; 54849 (Box 289, Folder 39)
  - NYU Opportunity Fellows Reception (NYU), 1988-11-14; 54847 (Box 289, Folder 40)
  - Bobst Awards in Arts and Letters (NYU), 1988-11-14; 54848 (Box 289, Folder 41)
  - "First Liberty" Forum Luncheon of the Williamsburg Charter Foundation, 1988-11-15; 54846 (Box 289, Folder 42)
  - Education Daily Consensus Panel on SATs, 1988-11-15; 54845 (Box 289, Folder 43)
  - Trustees Scholars Dinner (NYU), 1988-11-16; 54844 (Box 289, Folder 44)
  - Los Angeles Alumni Reception (Beverly Hills, CA), 1988-11-21; 54843 (Box 290, Folder 1)
  - Brademas Receives 1988 Axios Man of the Year Award (Beverly Hills, CA), 1988-11-22; 54842 (Box 290, Folder 2)
  - Economic Development Institute of the World Bank Seminar on Quality and Efficiency of Higher Education (Brasilia, Brazil), 1988-11-27; 54841 (Box 290, Folder 3)
  - "The Vision of Hubert Humphrey: Education for a Better Tomorrow," 10th Anniversary Hubert H. Humphrey North-South Fellowship Program (Rio de Janeiro, Brazil), 1988-12-01; 54840 (Box 290, Folder 4)
  - "The Vision of Hubert Humphrey: Education for a Better Tomorrow," 10th Anniversary Hubert H. Humphrey North-South Fellowship Program (Rio de Janeiro, Brazil), 1988-12-01 (Box 101, Video 36)
  - Reception for the Book: America in Theory (NYU), 1988-12-05; 54839 (Box 290, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Service Reception (NYU), 1988-12-05, 1988-12-07; 54838 (Box 290, Folder 6)
  - Medical Center Board Executive Committee Meeting RESTRICTED, 1988-12-06 (Box 102, Folder 23)
  - Introduction of Congressman Dan Rostenkowski at a Conference on Taxation Dinner (New York, NY), 1988-12-06; 54837 (Box 290, Folder 7)
  - University Senate Meeting (NYU), 1988-12-08; 54835 (Box 290, Folder 8)
  - Arthur L. Carter Hall Dedication (NYU), 1988-12-12; 54834 (Box 290, Folder 9)
  - NYU Board of Trustees Meeting RESTRICTED, 1988-12-12 (Box 102, Folder 24)
  - Introduction for Speros Vryonis Lecture on the 900th Anniversary of St. John Monastery (New York, NY), 1988-12-13; 54831 (Box 290, Folder 10)
  - Dinner Honoring Mr. and Mrs. Leonard N. Stern (NYU), 1988-12-13; 54832 (Box 290, Folder 11)
  - Testimony at a Hearing of the Subcommittee on Education and Health of the Joint Economic Committee (Washington, D.C.), 1988-12-14; 54830 (Box 290, Folder 12)
  - Faculty Council Luncheon (NYU), 1988-12-15; 54829 (Box 290, Folder 13)
  - Reaction Memo to American Council on Education Document "Issues in the 101st Congress", 1988-12-21; 54828 (Box 290, Folder 14)
  - Letter Bidding Farewell to Father Raymond Rafferty (NYU), 1989-01-11; 54826 (Box 290, Folder 15)
  - Annual Meeting of the American Council on Education (San Diego, CA), 1989-01-20; 54825 (Box 290, Folder 16)
  - Documentation Re: Thomas Eagleton Response to Harold Brown on "Congress and Foreign Policy", 1989-01-20; 54824 (Box 290, Folder 17)
  - Medical Center Press Conference Announcing The Tisch Hospital (NYU), 1989-01-25; 54823 (Box 290, Folder 18)
  - NYU Alumni Reception in Atlanta (Atlanta, GA), 1989-01-27; 54822 (Box 290, Folder 19)
  - Institute of Fine Arts Board Meeting RESTRICTED, 1989-01-30 (Box 102, Folder 25)
  - Onassis Center for Hellenic Studies Dinner (NYU), 1989-01-30; 54820 (Box 290, Folder 20)
  - Committee of the Year 2000 Meeting (New York, NY), 1989-01-31; 54819 (Box 290, Folder 21)
  - Op-Ed Piece -- "An Olive Branch Within Easy Reach", 1989-02; 54818 (Box 290, Folder 22)
  - Getty Center for Education in the Arts National Conference (Los Angeles, CA), 1989-02-02; 54817 (Box 290, Folder 23)
  - Essay Submission for "Berlin/New York" Project, 1989-02-03; 54816 (Box 290, Folder 24)
  - Robert Wood Johnson Press Conference (NYU), 1989-02-06; 54815 (Box 290, Folder 25)
  - McGeorge Bundy Book Reception (NYU), 1989-02-06; 54813 (Box 290, Folder 26)
  - NYU Board of Trustees Meeting RESTRICTED, 1989-02-06 (Box 102, Folder 26)
  - Testimony Supplement Statement Re: Student Loan Default Problems, 1989-02-08; 54812 (Box 290, Folder 27)
  - University Senate Meeting (NYU), 1989-02-09; 54811 (Box 290, Folder 28)
  - Brademas Receiving the Hellene of the Year Award at the Athenian Ball (New York, NY), 1989-02-15; 54810 (Box 290, Folder 29)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science Board of Overseers Meeting (NYU), 1989-02-16; 54809 (Box 290, Folder 30)
  - "Education for a Strong & Sure America," Mid-Atlantic Club Luncheon, 1989-02-16; 54808 (Box 291, Folder 1)
  - President's Council Reception (New York, NY), 1989-02-22 (Box 291, Folder 2)
  - Brademas Interview, Broadcast on FNN, 1989-02-22; 54807 (Box 291, Folder 3)
  - Essay, "The Challenge of International Education," Published in the Journal of International Affairs, 1989-02-22; 54805 (Box 291, Folder 4)
  - United Way and NYU Community Fund Campaign Reception, 2020-01-23; 54804 (Box 291, Folder 5)
  - Luncheon Honoring the Comptroller General (NYU), 1989-02-27; 54803 (Box 291, Folder 6)
  - NYU Day Events in Albany, 1989-02-28; 54802 (Box 291, Folder 7)
  - Metro Center Benefit Luncheon (New York, NY), 1989-03-01; 54801 (Box 291, Folder 8)
  - NYC Partnership / Urban Research Center Breakfast (NYU), 1989-03-02; 54800 (Box 291, Folder 9)
  - Medical Center Board Meeting RESTRICTED, 1989-03-02 (Box 102, Folder 27)
  - Afternoon at Washington Square, 1989-03-05; 54798 (Box 291, Folder 10)
  - Alumni Council Meeting (NYU), 1989-03-08; 54797 (Box 291, Folder 11)
  - Comments Preceding the Ramasco Lecture, Department of History (NYU), 1989-03-09; 54796 (Box 291, Folder 12)
  - Aphrodisias Colloquium (NYU), 1989-03-09; 54795 (Box 291, Folder 13)
  - University Senate Meeting (NYU), 1989-03-09; 54794 (Box 291, Folder 14)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting RESTRICTED, 1989-03-13 (Box 102, Folder 27)
  - 22nd Annual Real Estate Institute Urban Leadership Award Dinner (New York, NY), 1989-03-15; 54792 (Box 291, Folder 15)
  - Faculty Council Luncheon (NYU), 1989-03-23; 54791 (Box 291, Folder 16)
  - Association of American Publishers Annual Meeting (Boca Raton, FL), 1989-03-30; 54789 (Box 291, Folder 17)
  - Luncheon Commemorating the Enthronement of Archbishop Iakovos (New York, NY), 1989-04-02; 54788 (Box 291, Folder 18)
  - Lecture and Dinner Honoring Lee Hamilton (NYU), 1989-04-03; 54787 (Box 291, Folder 19)
  - Medical Center Board Meeting RESTRICTED, 1989-04-04 (Box 102, Folder 28)
  - NYU Family Dinner Hosted by David Kriser, 1989-04-05; 54785 (Box 291, Folder 20)
  - Presidential Scholars Reception (NYU), 1989-04-08; 54784 (Box 291, Folder 21)
  - Annenberg Program Debate, 1989-04-10; 54783 (Box 291, Folder 22)
  - Reception to Honor Lewis and Jack Rudin (NYU), 1989-04-11; 54782 (Box 291, Folder 23)
  - NYU Alumni Reception (Stamford, CT), 1989-04-12; 54781 (Box 291, Folder 24)
  - Reception Honoring Chinua Achebe (NYU), 1989-04-13; 54780 (Box 291, Folder 25)
  - University Senate Meeting (NYU), 1989-04-13; 54779 (Box 291, Folder 26)
  - Conference on "Books, Babies, and Libraries: Making the Connection," New York Public Library (New York, NY), 1989-04-13; 54778 (Box 291, Folder 27)
  - Meeting of the Northeastern Association of Graduate Schools (Albany, NY), 1989-04-14; 54776 (Box 291, Folder 28)
  - Religion and Public Policy Conference Panel, Georgetown University (Washington, D.C.), 1989-04-14 (Box 291, Folder 29)
  - Law School Revue (NYU), 1989-04-15; 54775 (Box 291, Folder 30)
  - Founders Day Honors Convocation (NYU), 1989-04-16; 54774 (Box 291, Folder 31)
  - Laudatio of the Honorable J. William Fulbright (Athens, Greece), 1989-04-21 and 1989-05; 54773 (Box 291, Folder 32)
  - Statement Delivered Before the Subcommittee on Energy & Water Development of the House Committee on Appropriations (Washington, D.C.), 1989-04-21 and 1989-05; 54771 (Box 291, Folder 33)
  - Statement Delivered Before the Subcommittee on Natural Resources, Agriculture, Research, & the Environment of the House Committee on Science, Space, and Technology (Washington, D.C.), 1989-04-21; 54770 (Box 291, Folder 34)
  - Conference on Abused Children (New York, NY), 1989-04-27; 54769 (Box 292, Folder 1)
  - Reception Honoring E.L. Doctorow (NYU), 1989-04-27; 54768 (Box 292, Folder 2)
  - NYU Metropolitan Studies Conference on Children (NYU), 1989-04-28; 54767 (Box 292, Folder 3)
  - "The Generational Contract: Educating All Our Youngsters for the 1990s," Carnegie Foundation for the Advancement of Teaching / Americans for Generational Equity Regional Conference, 1989-04-28; 54766 (Box 292, Folder 4)
  - Washington Square Arch 100th Anniversary Celebration, 1989-04-30; 54765 (Box 292, Folder 5)
  - "Is the Agenda for Science Too Important To Be Left to Scientists?", Nexus Article, May 1989; 54764 (Box 292, Folder 6)
  - Advances at NYU, May 1989; 54762 (Box 292, Folder 7)
  - Dinner Honoring Robert Maxwell (NYU), 1989-05-01; 54763 (Box 292, Folder 8)
  - College of Arts and Science Heads (CASH) Luncheon (NYU), 1989-05-02; 54761 (Box 292, Folder 9)
  - Remarks for Dean Harvey Stedmana for Taping of PBS Show, Author, Author, 1989-05-02; 54760 (Box 292, Folder 10)
  - School of Education, Health, Nursing, and the Arts Professions Prism Award Luncheon Honoring Robert Maxwell (New York, NY), 1989-05-03; 54759 (Box 292, Folder 11)
  - Alumni Council Meeting (NYU), 1989-05-03; 54758 (Box 292, Folder 12)
  - University Senate Meeting (NYU), 1989-05-04; 54757 (Box 292, Folder 13)
  - Greek Press of the Diaspora Dinner (NYU), 1989-05-06; 54756 (Box 292, Folder 14)
  - "Some Social Implications of New Technologies," Omni Desk Conference (NYU), 1989-05-08; 54755 (Box 292, Folder 15)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting RESTRICTED, 1989-05-08 (Box 102, Folder 29)
  - Institute of Fine Arts Board Meeting RESTRICTED, 1989-05-11 (Box 102, Folder 30)
  - Presentation of the 25-Year Service Awards (NYU), 1989-05-11; 54752 (Box 292, Folder 16)
  - NYU Community Fund, 1989-05-16; 54750 (Box 292, Folder 17)
  - Trustees Pre-Commencement Dinner (NYU), 1989-05-17; 54749 (Box 292, Folder 18)
  - Alumni Commencement Breakfast (NYU), 1989-05-18; 54747 (Box 292, Folder 19)
  - Medical Center Commencement (NYU), 1989-05-18; 54748 (Box 292, Folder 20)
  - Ceremony Honoring Albert Gallatin Medalist Taggart Whipple (NYU), 1989-05-18; 54746 (Box 292, Folder 21)
  - 157th Commencement Exercises (NYU), 1989-05-18; 54745 (Box 292, Folder 22)
  - Honorary Degree Citations, 1989-05-18 (Box 292, Folder 23)
  - "Reflections on Congress" at the White Burkett Miller Center of Public Affairs at the University of Virginia, 1989-05-19; 54743 (Box 292, Folder 24)
  - Brasenose College Charitable Foundation Dinner (NYU), 1989-05-30; 54742 (Box 292, Folder 25)
  - Herbert R. Silverman Scholarship Fund Reception (NYU), 1989-06-01; 54741 (Box 292, Folder 26)
  - Wayne E. Hirschkorn Memorial Fund Reception (NYU), 1989-06-06; 54738 (Box 292, Folder 27)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting RESTRICTED, 1989-06-05 (Box 102, Folder 31)
  - Medical Center Board Meeting RESTRICTED, 1989-06-06 (Box 102, Folder 32)
  - Breakfast Meeting of the Gallatin Associates & President's Council (NYU), 1989-06-07; 54736 (Box 292, Folder 28)
  - Cultural & Educational Agreement Between the U.S. & Spain Reception, United State Information Agency (Washington, D.C.), 1989-06-07; 54737 (Box 292, Folder 29)
  - Statement for Press Kit, Archivists Round Table of Metropolitan New York, 1989-06-13; 54735 (Box 292, Folder 30)
  - Message to NYU / Yugoslavia Marketing Seminar Message, 1989-06-16; 54734 (Box 292, Folder 31)
  - "Higher Education in the 1990s: Prospects & Problems," Gannett Center Conference, 1989-06-18; 54733 (Box 292, Folder 32)
  - Medical Center Faculty Meeting (NYU), 1989-06-19; 54732 (Box 292, Folder 33)
  - Penthouse Dinner Honoring Pascual Maragall (NYU), 1989-06-21; 54731 (Box 292, Folder 34)
  - Article in Oxford Today, 1989-06-23; 54730 (Box 292, Folder 35)
  - Silver Shalis Cruise, 1989-06-28; 54729 (Box 292, Folder 36)
  - Nomination of Marian Wright Edelman for McGraw-Hill Prize, 1989-06-30; 54728 (Box 292, Folder 37)
  - Response to Newsday Editorial, 1989-07-06; 54726 (Box 292, Folder 38)
  - Funding for Fairness (NYU), 1989-08-02; 54725 (Box 292, Folder 39)
  - Introduction to Medical Center Brochure, 1989-08-22; 54724 (Box 292, Folder 40)
  - Undergraduate Convocation, 1989-09-05; 54723 (Box 292, Folder 41)
  - New York City Mayoral Candidate Debate Introductions (NYU), 1989-09-06; 54722 (Box 292, Folder 42)
  - Op-ed on Drugs, 1989-09-06; 54721 (Box 295, Folder 1)
  - Medical Center Board of Trustees Meeting RESTRICTED, 1989-09-07 (Box 102, Folder 33)
  - Community Service Society Retired Senior Volunteer Program (New York, NY), 1989-09-14; 54719 (Box 295, Folder 2)
  - Introduction of Senator Daniel Patrick Moynihan at National Association of Independent Colleges and Universities Leadership Conference, 1990-09-14; 54718 (Box 295, Folder 3)
  - Board of Trustees Executive Meeting RESTRICTED, 1989-09-18 (Box 102, Folder 34)
  - Caldwell College 50th Anniversary Convocation (Caldwell, NJ), 1989-09-20; 54716 (Box 295, Folder 4)
  - Covenant of Peace Award Dinner, 1989-09-20; 54715 (Box 295, Folder 5)
  - Dedication of the Henry Viscardi High School (Albertson, NY), 1989-09-21; 54714 (Box 295, Folder 6)
  - Hagop Kevorkian Center Cultural Heritage Conference (NYU), 1989-09-21; 54713 (Box 295, Folder 7)
  - World Management Congress, 1989-09-21; 54712 (Box 295, Folder 8)
  - Georgetown University President Inaugural Luncheon (Washington, D.C.), 1989-09-23; 54711 (Box 295, Folder 9)
  - Graduate School of Public Administration Naming Press Conference, 1989-09-25; 54710 (Box 295, Folder 10)
  - Memorial Service for Sidney Hook (NYU), 1989-09-25; 54709 (Box 295, Folder 11)
  - Tokyo Broadcasting System Luncheon (NYU), 1989-09-26; 54708 (Box 295, Folder 12)
  - Alumni Relations Program Reception (NYU), 1989-09-26; 54707 (Box 295, Folder 13)
  - New Graduate Students Reception (NYU), 1989-09-27; 54706 (Box 295, Folder 14)
  - Chet Huntley Memorial Lecture, 1989-09-27; 54705 (Box 295, Folder 15)
  - International Radio and Television Foundation (IRTF) Benefit Dinner (New York, NY), 1989-09-28; 54704 (Box 295, Folder 16)
  - Luncheon Honoring Jorge Semprun (NYU), 1989-09-29; 54703 (Box 295, Folder 17)
  - Humanities Council Readings on Greenwich Village, 1989-10-03; 54702 (Box 295, Folder 18)
  - University Senate Meeting (NYU), 1989-10-05; 54701 (Box 295, Folder 19)
  - Events Commemorating President George Vassiliou, 1989-10-05; 54699 (Box 295, Folder 20)
  - Medical Center Board Meeting RESTRICTED, 1989-10-10 (Box 102, Folder 35)
  - University Athletics Association Presidents' Press Reception (NYU), 1989-10-11; 54697 (Box 295, Folder 21)
  - Alumni Council Meeting, 1989-10-11; 54696 (Box 295, Folder 22)
  - New Jersey Regional Alumni Reception (Short Hills, NJ), 1989-10-12; 54695 (Box 295, Folder 23)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting RESTRICTED, 1989-10-12 (Box 102, Folder 36)
  - Tisch School of the Arts Luncheon Honoring Soviet Filmmakers (NYU), 1989-10-17; 54693 (Box 295, Folder 24)
  - Inaugural Reception for Arthur Imperatore Professorship (NYU), 1989-10-30; 54692 (Box 295, Folder 25)
  - Real Estate Institute Campaign Announcement (NYU), 1989-10-31; 54691 (Box 295, Folder 26)
  - Dinner Honoring Ralph Marino (NYU), 1989-10-31; 54690 (Box 295, Folder 27)
  - Lecture Celebrating the Nancy Hanks Endowment at Duke University (Durham, NC), 1989-11-02; 54689 (Box 295, Folder 28)
  - Temple Emanu-El Forum (New York, NY), 1989-11-05; 54688 (Box 295, Folder 29)
  - Address at the Donald MacNaughton Symposium, 1989-11-08; 54687 (Box 295, Folder 30)
  - All-University Dinner Dance (NYU), 1989-11-08; 54686 (Box 295, Folder 31)
  - University Senate Meeting (NYU), 1989-11-09; 54685 (Box 295, Folder 32)
  - Elmer Holmes Bobst Memorial Room Dedication (NYU), 1989-11-09; 54684 (Box 295, Folder 33)
  - United Hellenic American Congress Dinner Dance (Chicago, IL), 1989-11-11; 54683 (Box 295, Folder 34)
  - Onassis Center Dedication (NYU), 1989-11-13; 54682 (Box 295, Folder 35)
  - Trustees Scholars Reception (NYU), 1989-11-15; 54681 (Box 295, Folder 36)
  - Center for Latin American and Caribbean Studies Luncheon (NYU), 1989-11-16; 54680 (Box 295, Folder 37)
  - Dinner Honoring Robert F. Wagner (NYU), 1989-11-16; 54679 (Box 295, Folder 38)
  - Luncheon Honoring Marie Schwartz, 1989-11-17; 54678 (Box 295, Folder 39)
  - Scholarship Foundation of St. Joseph County Meeting (South Bend, IN), 1989-11-19; 54677 (Box 295, Folder 40)
  - Lecture by Jose Maria Maravall (NYU), 1989-11-20; 54676 (Box 295, Folder 41)
  - Washington Square Park Gift Acknowledgment (NYU), 1989-11-21; 54675 (Box 295, Folder 42)
  - Middle States Association of Collegiate Registrars Meeting (Atlantic City, NJ), 1989-11-27; 54674 (Box 296, Folder 1)
  - Annual Management Conference of the General Accounting Office (Chantilly, VA), 1989-11-29; 54673 (Box 296, Folder 2)
  - Arthur Lehning Tribute Chapter in Voor Arthur Lehning, 1989-12 (Box 296, Folder 3)
  - Medical Center Board Meeting RESTRICTED, 1989-12-05; 54672 (Box 297, Folder 1)
  - Dinner Honoring Elie Wiesel (NYU), 1989-12-06; 54671 (Box 296, Folder 4)
  - University Senate Meeting (NYU), 1989-12-07; 54670 (Box 296, Folder 5)
  - Dr. Howard A. Rusk Memorial Service (NYU), 1989-12-07; 54669 (Box 296, Folder 6)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting RESTRICTED, 1989-12-11 (Box 297, Folder 2)
  - Ed Koch Reception (NYU), 1989-12-11; 54668 (Box 296, Folder 7)
  - Education Week Interview, 1989-12-15; 54666 (Box 296, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Council Luncheon (NYU), 1989-12-14; 54665 (Box 296, Folder 9)
  - School of Education, Health, Nursing, and the Arts Professions Faculty Meeting (NYU), 1989-12-18; 54664 (Box 296, Folder 10)
  - Carnegie Council Breakfast (New York, NY), 1989-12-19; 54663 (Box 296, Folder 11)
  - Message from the President for Staff Handbook, January 1990; 54661 (Box 296, Folder 12)
  - Dinner Honoring Asa and Susan Briggs (NYU), 1990-01-05; 54659 (Box 296, Folder 13)
  - Medical Center Board Meeting RESTRICTED, 1990-01-09 (Box 297, Folder 3)
  - New York Regional Office of the General Accounting Office Meeting (New York, NY), 1990-01-17; 54658 (Box 296, Folder 14)
  - Community Service / Youth Service Dinner (NYU), 1990-01-18; 54657 (Box 296, Folder 15)
  - Texaco Roundtable Luncheon (White Plains, NY), 1990-01-18; 54656 (Box 296, Folder 16)
  - USA Today Luncheon (Arlington, VA), 1990-01-19; 54655 (Box 296, Folder 17)
  - New York / Italy Medical Symposium (New York, NY), 1990-01-20; 54654 (Box 296, Folder 18)
  - Global Affairs Institute Keynote Address (New York, NY), 1990-01-21; 54653 (Box 296, Folder 19)
  - Council for Advancement and Support of Education Middle Atlantic District II Annual Conference Keynote Address (New York, NY), 1990-01-22; 54652 (Box 296, Folder 20)
  - Faculty Resource Network Luncheon (NYU), 1990-01-25; 54651 (Box 296, Folder 21)
  - Institute of Fine Arts Board Meeting RESTRICTED, 1990-01-13 (Box 297, Folder 4)
  - Mediterranean Quarterly Editorial, 1990-02-01 (Box 296, Folder 22)
  - Florida Alumni Reception (Boca Raton, FL), 1990-02-01; 54649 (Box 296, Folder 23)
  - Real Estate Institute Dinner (NYU), 1990-02-06; 54648 (Box 296, Folder 24)
  - University Senate Meeting (NYU), 1990-02-08; 54647 (Box 296, Folder 25)
  - Celia Farris Dinner (Palm Beach, FL), 1990-02-10; 54646 (Box 296, Folder 26)
  - Response to University of Oklahoma Press Re: The International Education Act of 1966 by Theodore M, Vestal, 1990-02-15; 54645 (Box 296, Folder 27)
  - Chicago Alumni Reception (Chicago, IL), 1990-02-18; 54644 (Box 296, Folder 28)
  - Urban Research Center Lunch (NYU), 1990-02-20; 54643 (Box 296, Folder 29)
  - Press Conference Announcing Grantees of the Robert Wood Johnson Foundation's "Fighting Back" Program (Washington, D.C.), 1990-02-21; 54642 (Box 296, Folder 30)
  - Messages for "Benefactors" Book, 1990-02-21; 54641 (Box 296, Folder 31)
  - Riklis Ackerman Dinner (New York, NY), 1990-02-22; 54640 (Box 296, Folder 32)
  - Op-ed for The Chronicle of Higher Education, 1990-02-23; 54639 (Box 296, Folder 33)
  - NYU in Albany Day (Albany, NY), 1990-02-27; 54638 (Box 296, Folder 34)
  - Reception Honoring Chancellor Joseph Fernandez (NYU), 1990-02-28; 54637 (Box 296, Folder 35)
  - Metro Center Benefit Luncheon (New York, NY), 1990-03-01; 54636 (Box 298, Folder 1)
  - Annual Archons Banquet (New York, NY), 1990-03-03; 54634 (Box 298, Folder 2)
  - Sunday at the Square (NYU), 1990-03-04; 54633 (Box 298, Folder 3)
  - National Institute of Social Sciences Luncheon (New York, NY), 1990-03-05; 54632 (Box 298, Folder 4)
  - Medical Center Board of Trustees Meeting RESTRICTED, 1990-03-06 (Box 297, Folder 5)
  - United Way / NYU Community Fund Campaign Reception, 1990-03-07; 54630 (Box 298, Folder 5)
  - Celebration Honoring Giulio Andreotti (NYU), 1990-03-08; 54629 (Box 298, Folder 6)
  - University Senate Meeting (NYU), 1990-03-08; 54628 (Box 298, Folder 7)
  - Hagop Kevorkian Center Luncheon (NYU), 1990-03-09; 54627 (Box 298, Folder 8)
  - Presentation of the John Jay Award to McGeorge Bundy (Albany, NY), 1990-03-12; 54626 (Box 298, Folder 9)
  - Charles Waldo Haskins Award Dinner (New York, NY), 1990-03-13; 54624 (Box 298, Folder 10)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting RESTRICTED, 1990-03-19 (Box 297, Folder 6)
  - Dr. Rita Sussmuth Lecture and Dinner (NYU), 1990-03-19 (Box 298, Folder 11)
  - Conference on Czech Literature and Culture (NYU), 1990-03-19; 54622 (Box 298, Folder 12)
  - Luncheon Honoring Julian Santamaria (NYU), 1990-03-19; 54621 (Box 298, Folder 13)
  - Conference on US-USSR Cooperation at the United Nations (NYU), 1990-03-20; 54618 (Box 298, Folder 14)
  - Luncheon Honoring Sir Raymond Hoffenberg (NYU), 1990-03-21; 54617 (Box 298, Folder 15)
  - Real Estate Institute Urban Leadership Award Dinner (New York, NY), 1990-03-21; 54616 (Box 298, Folder 16)
  - Faculty Council Luncheon (NYU), 1990-03-22; 54615 (Box 298, Folder 17)